To save the future he must reshape the past.
Predestination is a science fiction, thriller film directed by Michael Spierig.
Predestination chronicles the life of a Temporal Agent sent on an intricate series of
time-travel journeys designed to prevent future killers from committing their crimes.
Now, on his final assignment, the Agent must stop the one criminal that has eluded him throughout
time and prevent a devastating attack in which thousands of lives will be lost.
The Bartender, played by Ethan Hawke.
The Unmarried Mother, played by Sarah Snook.
Mr. Robertson, played by Noah Taylor.
Mr. Miles, played by Christopher Kirby.
Mrs. Stapleton, played by Madeleine West.
Dr. Belfort, played by Jim Knobeloch.
Predestination is a 2014 Australian science fiction thriller film
written and directed by Michael and Peter Spierig.
The film stars Ethan Hawke, Sarah Snook, and Noah Taylor, and is based on
the 1959 short story " '—All You Zombies—'" by Robert A.
It follows a time traveling agent who is sent on his final mission to apprehend the elusive "Fizzle
Bomber", a terrorist responsible for dozens of bombings across history, before its next attack.
The film explores themes of mission, orphanage,
pregnancy, bomber, secret organization.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.